[music]
[音乐]
Hello and welcome to section four of
您好，欢迎阅读第4节
lesson one. In this part we're going to look at some of
第一课。在这一部分中，我们将研究一些
the new interfaces that have been added
已添加的新接口
in JDK 8, specifically in the java.util.function package
在JDK 8中，特别是在java.util.function包中
that are very useful, especially when we come to doing things like the streams API.
这非常有用，尤其是当我们要执行流API之类的事情时。
The
的
java.util.function package provides us with
java.util.function包为我们提供了
a very well-defined set of general-purpose
一组定义明确的通用
functional interfaces. These are places where we can use Lambda expressions,
函数式接口。这些是我们可以使用Lambda表达式的地方，
because they have one abstract method. We looked at this in the previous section
因为它们只有一种抽象方法。我们在上一节中介绍了这一点
about the idea that we needed only one abstract method.
关于我们只需要一种抽象方法的想法。
All of these interfaces are functional interfaces, they have
所有这些接口都是函数式接口，它们具有
one abstract method. What we find is that
一种抽象方法。我们发现的是
they are used extensively in a lot of the Java class libraries,
它们在许多Java类库中得到了广泛使用，
so you find them used a lot in the stream API that we’ll talk about in
因此您会发现它们在我们将在其中讨论的流API中使用了很多
lesson two, but there are also a number of other places where they’ve
第二课，但在其他许多地方
been added as parameters to different methods
作为参数添加到不同的方法
where we've included new things in the JDK 8
我们在JDK 8中包含了新内容
class libraries. What we’re going to talk about in this
类库。我们将在此谈论什么
section is the generic form of these interfaces.
部分是这些接口的通用形式。
If you look at the package itself what you'll find are that there are
如果您看一下包装本身，就会发现有
numerous versions of what I'm going to talk about
我要谈论的众多版本
which are type-specific. They’ll be double versions, int versions, long versions, and
是特定于类型的。它们将是双重版本，整数版本，长版本和
object versions as well. Once you've
对象版本。一旦你
reviewed this section of the the lesson, go and have a look at the actual
回顾了本节的这一节，然后去看看实际的
package information, have a look at all the different types, and you'll see what I
打包信息，看看所有不同的类型，您会看到我
mean by the
意思是
various type-specific versions. The first one we’re
各种类型的特定版本。我们第一个
going to look at is called a consumer, and this is essentially an operation, which
要看的叫做消费者，这本质上是一个操作，
takes a single value and, as the name would
取一个值，就像名字一样
imply, consumes it. It doesn't return
暗示，消耗它。它不回来
a result. We take the value that’s passed to it, we do something with it, but we don't
结果。我们采用传递给它的价值，我们用它做一些事情，但是我们不这样做
generate a result.
产生结果。
Very simple example here; the
这里的例子很简单；的
parameter that’s being passed is a string s, and we’re consuming
传递的参数是字符串s，我们正在使用
that by printing it out using system.out.println
通过使用system.out.println将其打印出来
We’re not using any return value,
我们没有使用任何返回值，
We’re not returning anything, it will be a void. There is
我们什么也不退货，这将是一个空白。有
also a second form of this called a BiConsumer and
也称为BiConsumer的第二种形式
what that will do is take two values as parameters
要做的是将两个值作为参数
and again, return no results. In terms of the interface itself, there are also some
再次，没有结果。就界面本身而言，还有一些
default methods, which will allow you to compose
默认方法，使您可以撰写
consumers. That means you can put them together
消费者。这意味着您可以将它们放在一起
to build up more complicated versions of a consumer
建立更复杂的消费者版本
so you could do something like consume something and then
所以你可以做一些像消耗一些东西然后
have another consumer off to its to actually consume the same variable
让另一个消费者去消费相同的变量
that's being passed
过去了
in different ways. If we look at
以不同的方式。如果我们看
an example of the BiConsumer what we’re doing here is we're passing in
BiConsumer的一个例子我们在这里做的是传递
two values, a key and a value from some kind of map,
两个值，一个键和某个映射中的值，
and then again we’re consuming it by printing out the
然后我们再次通过打印出
values of key as a key and then the value
键的值作为键，然后是值
as a value. The
作为价值。的
next one that we’ll look at is the supplier. What this does,
我们要看的下一个是供应商。这是做什么的
again as the name would imply, is supplies results.
顾名思义，这再次是供应结果。
It's really kind of the opposite of a Consumer. Consumer
确实与消费者相反。消费者
takes a value that’s passed to it and doesn't generate a result;
接受传递给它的值，并且不生成结果；
the supplier doesn't take a parameter
供应商不带参数
passed to it, there are no parameters, and it returns
传递给它，没有参数，它返回
some kind of value. In this case we’ve got
某种价值。在这种情况下，我们有
a very simple example where we’re not passing any values
一个非常简单的示例，其中我们没有传递任何值
because we don’t need any values and it will return
因为我们不需要任何值，它将返回
whatever createLogMessage: is going to generate for us.
任何createLogMessage：都会为我们生成。
Moving on,
继续，
we then have the idea of a function,
然后我们有了一个功能的想法，
and you can think of this in the same way as like a mathematical function.
您可以像数学函数一样来思考这个问题。
A function is something that takes one argument,
函数是需要一个参数的事物，
does something, and returns a result.
做某事，并返回结果。
It's a one to one
这是一对一的
function. Input, does something with it,
功能。输入，用它做点什么，
returns a result. In the case of function
返回结果。在功能的情况下
it has two type parameters, generic type parameters, T and R,
它有两个类型参数，通用类型参数T和R，
which means that the type of the argument and the result
这意味着参数的类型和结果
may be different, can be the same, but may be different. There’s also,
可以不同，可以相同，但可以不同。还有，
in the same way that we have a BiConsumer, there's another
与我们拥有BiConsumer的方式一样，还有另一个
version of this which is called BiFunction. This is one that takes
此版本称为BiFunction。这是需要的
two arguments and returns a result. Again
两个参数并返回结果。再次
in this case all of those types can be different,
在这种情况下，所有这些类型都可以不同，
so the types of the two parameters and return type can be different. Again,
因此两个参数的类型和返回类型可以不同。再次，
this has some useful default methods that you can use to compose
这有一些有用的默认方法，您可以用来编写
functions. There’s two of those; one is compose and one is
职能。有两个。一个是组成，一个是
andThen. To determine which of those you use
接着。确定您使用哪个
depends on whether you want the
取决于您是否想要
second form of the function to be applied before
在此之前应用的功能的第二种形式
the main function or after it.Compose will apply the
主要功能或之后的功能。compose将应用
new function before applying the function that’s been defined,
新功能，然后再应用已定义的功能，
andThen will apply the function that’s been defined
然后将应用已定义的功能
and then apply another function to it. Example here
然后对其应用另一个功能。这里的例子
of a function is simply to take our student, s,
函数的作用仅仅是让我们的学生
and to get the name so the input parameter is a student, s,
并获取名称，以便输入参数为学生s，
and the output is whatever the name of that student is
输出是那个学生的名字
as a string. In terms of a BiFunction
作为字符串。就BiFunction而言
we can take two arguments, in this case a string which is the name
我们可以接受两个参数，在这种情况下是一个字符串
and a student s and we will return
和一个学生的，我们将返回
a new object of type teacher which uses both
一个教师类型的新对象，它同时使用
the name and the student as the
名字和学生为
values that we’re going to use for constructor.
我们将用于构造函数的值。
The UnaryOperator. This is really
UnaryOperator。这真的是
like a function, but it's a specific type
就像一个函数，但这是一种特定的类型
Of function. In this case it's the same as a function
功能。在这种情况下，它与函数相同
where both the parameter
其中两个参数
and the return type are the same. It's
和返回类型相同。它的
kind of like the subclass of function in some ways.
在某种程度上类似于函数的子类。
Here we’ve got an example where we’re passing it a string, s,
在这里，我们有一个传递字符串s的示例，
and we’re returning the lower case version of the string,
然后我们返回字符串的小写版本，
so we’re passing in a string and returning in a string. Both are the same type.
所以我们传入一个字符串并返回一个字符串。两者是同一类型。
In the same way that we have
以我们拥有的相同方式
a UnaryOperator that is a special form of the
UnaryOperator，它是
function, there’s also a binary operator which is a specialized form
函数，还有一个二进制运算符，它是一种特殊形式
of BiFunction. Again, rather than having
BiFunction。再说一次
potentially different type arguments and results in this case
在这种情况下，可能存在不同类型的参数和结果
the two parameters that we pass to the apply method
我们传递给apply方法的两个参数
are the same as the return type, so T is used
与返回类型相同，因此使用T
throughout all three different variables there. We can see an example of that
贯穿所有三个不同的变量。我们可以看到一个例子
here,
这里，
where we're passing two strings as our parameters
我们在传递两个字符串作为参数
and then we have a body our Lambda expression
然后我们有一个Lambda表达式主体
which is comparing the length of the strings and returning whichever is the
这是比较字符串的长度并返回两者中的任意一个
longest,
最长，
of either x or y.
x或y的
The type of the return is a string, the type of the two parameters is a string,
返回的类型是一个字符串，两个参数的类型是一个字符串，
so it is a BinaryOperator, Predicate.
因此它是BinaryOperator，谓词。
We’ve already seen Predicate when we looked at functional interfaces
当我们看函数式接口时，我们已经看过谓词
and, again this is release a specialized form
再次，这是发布专门的表格
of a function because, in this case it’s a function that
的功能，因为在这种情况下，
always returns a boolean. Takes one argument, but
总是返回一个布尔值。有一个论点，但是
always returns a boolean to indicate whether or not
始终返回一个布尔值以指示是否
the predicate is true of false.
谓词为真，为假。
Again, there is a two-argument
同样，有两个参数
form of that called BiPredicate, which takes two
BiPredicate的形式，它需要两个
arguments and returns a boolean, same as you have a BiFunction,
参数并返回一个布尔值，就像您具有BiFunction一样，
so you can do the same with a BiPredicate. Again,
因此，您可以对BiPredicate执行相同的操作。再次，
there are some useful default and static methods that you can use to combine
有一些有用的默认方法和静态方法可以组合使用
these things,
这些东西，
so you can do the typical binary kind of
所以你可以做典型的二进制
operations you can do and, you can do or you can do negate.
您可以执行的操作，可以执行的操作或可以进行取反的操作。
Then, you can also have a thing to say isEqual.
然后，您也可以说isEqual。
An example of that is with the one we've already seen,
我们已经看到的例子就是一个例子
where we’re passing a parameter, student s, and we’re returning
在我们传递参数s的地方，我们返回
whether the graduation year is 2011, so that's a
毕业年份是2011年，那是
predicate Lambda expression where we compare the graduation year to 2011
谓词Lambda表达式，我们将毕业年份与2011年进行比较
and return a boolean. As an example of a
并返回一个布尔值。作为一个例子
BiPredicate in this case we have
在这种情况下，BiPredicate
a situation where for the find method in files
一种在文件中查找方法的情况
we pass in a path and an attribute
我们传递路径和属性
and then we can define how we want to use those
然后我们可以定义如何使用这些
to determine whether the files will be used
确定是否将使用文件
in terms of our stream of results. In this case what we're doing is we're
就我们的结果而言。在这种情况下，我们正在做的是
taking
服用
the string value of the path, the name of
路径的字符串值，名称
the path we've got, testing whether ends with dot JS to see if we’ve got
我们的路径，测试是否以点JS结尾，以查看是否
a JavaScript file
一个JavaScript文件
and then also testing to see whether the size of the file
然后还要测试以查看文件的大小
is over one kilobyte in size. We’re using both the parameters
超过一千字节。我们同时使用了两个参数
that are being passed in terms of that BiPredicate. To summarize section
根据该BiPredicate传递。总结部分
four, the function package, which is new in JDK 8
四，功能包，这是JDK 8中的新增功能
provides us with a very useful range of functional interfaces.
为我们提供了非常有用的函数式接口。
As we'll see in Lesson two these
我们将在第二课中看到这些
are used extensively in the streams API
在流API中广泛使用
but there are also a number of other places where we use them
但是我们在其他许多地方也使用它们
and we’ll see those later in this particular lesson. Although you can
我们将在本课程的稍后部分看到这些内容。虽然可以
define your own extensions to the function package it’s probably very
为功能包定义自己的扩展，可能非常
unlikely that you will need to.
您不太可能需要。
You’ll find that the  ones that have been defined will cover
您会发现已定义的内容将涵盖
pretty much any situation that you're going need in terms of basic
基本而言，您几乎需要的任何情况
functional interfaces for these types of things.
这些类型的事物的函数式接口。
And that is the end of this section of the lesson.
至此，本节的结尾。